A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics, Series P FA351
Rockefeller Archive Center
- K General (Box 9, Folder 231)
  Kaarl, Melinda (Miss): 1967, appeal. Kampmann, Flora (Mrs.): 1970, former National Committeewoman from Texas, trip to Los Angeles. Kabis, Dorothy Andrews (The Honorable): 1971, Department of the Treasury, Fiscal Service, sends NAR congratulations, NAR seeks information on Eisenhower silver dollars. Kaplan, H. Eliot: 1961-1963, President, Civil Service Commission - State Department of Civil Service, Elmer A. Carter, Special Assistant to the Governor on Intergroup Relations. Kaplan, Joseph: 1967-1968, appeal. Karionk, Marie: 1960, thank you to NAR for Museum of Modern Art membership. Karlene, Michael M.: 1960, seeks NAR assistance. Karram, Lila (Miss): 1965, thanks from NAR for afghan. Kayser, Lee L.: 1969, thanks to NAR for permisssion to ride in Pocantico Hills. Keane, Bob: 1969, personal correspondence. Keenan, Edward J.: 1968, Presidential Campaign. Kelly, Robert F.: 1973, thanks for luncheon for Commissioners on Cable Television from other states. Kemper, James S.: 1959, Chairman of the Board, Kemper Insurance; sends Report of Special Legislative Committee on the Massachusetts Compulsory Automobile Insurance System. Kempton, Murray: 1966, thank you from NAR. Kennedy, J. P. (Mrs.): 1971, NAR appeance on David Frost Show. Kerrison, F. R. (Mrs.): 1966, Christmas greetings. Keyser, F. Ray (Jr.): 1966-1967, Albany South Mall Project. Khrushchev, Nikita S.: 1959, thanks, visit to United States. Kimball, Robert M.: 1962, appeal for job at Rockefeller Foundation, Dartmouth graduate. Kingsbury-Smith, Joseph: 1967, European Director of Hearst Corporation, seeks appointment with NAR. Kinsky, Ferdinand: 1970, European scholar, appeal, declined. Kinter, William R.: 1970, Director, Foreign Policy Research Institute, University of Pennsylvania; sends report on "The Middle East: The Escalation is on the Other Side." Kirk, Claude: 1967, Governor of Florida, thanks for conference. Kirschenbaum, Irving: 1964, member, First Judicial District, New York State Board of Social Welfare; Assembly Bill Intro # 5282, NAR's thank you for Steuben crystal. Kirstein, Lincoln: 1965, Director, New York City Ballet. Kistler, D. F. (Mrs.): 1970, NAR's thank you for oil painting. Klein, Julius: 1973, Industrial Location Services of the State of New York. Knight, Bruce Winston (Mrs.): 1962, son working at Rockefeller University, generous comments and good wishes. Knight, Frances G. (Miss): 1970, Director, Passport Office. NAR's thank you for new passport. Knight, Gordon R.: 1967, invitation to visit Hawaii Trails. Knopf, Alfred A.: 1962-1966, trip to Los Angeles, trustees for State University in Harrison raised antagonism to NAR, Knopf emphatic defender, sends book. Knowles, Howard N.: 1960, Mrs. Grace Van Dyne Merrill receiving monthly gift from John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Koch, Richard H.: 1968, Secretary, Museum of Modern Art, Resolutions Meeting. Koegel, Otto E.: 1970, Urban Development Corporation, Bill Strawbridge. Kohlberg, Alfred: 1959, Chairman, American China Policy Association, re: Chiang Kai-shek sister-in-law and her Communist stand. Kohler, Foy D.: 1959, Acting Assistant Secretary of State for European Affairs. Kramer, Jay: 1966, appeal. Krekeler, Heinz L.: 1963, Atlantic Partnership. Future of Federalism. Kresky, Edward M.: 1965, NAR staff, leaving for Metropolitan Commuter Transportation Authority, thanks NAR. Kriendler, Peter: 1962-1970, President, Twenty-One Club, birthday wishes. Kross, Anna M.: 1965, Commissioner Department of Corrections, City of New York, protest. Krulewitch, Melvin L.: 1959-1967, Chairman, New York State Division of State Athletic Commission, personal correspondence. Kupperman, Theodore R.: 1971, Justice, Supreme Court of the State of New York, appeal.
- Keating, Kenneth B. (The Honorable), 1959-1972 (Box 9, Folder 232)
  Leave of absence for Hugh Morrow and Charles Potter, Inner Circle Dinner, Manchester rally, speaking in California, Alfalfa Club Dinner, election of Keating to the Court of Appeals, appeal for Carmine de Sapio, personal correspondence.
- Kemeny, John G., 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 233)
  President, Dartmouth College, appeal, campus coed plans, Alumni Fund gift.
- Kendall, Donald M., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  Chairman of the Board, Pepsico, Frito-Lay to locate in Broome County.
- Kennedy, John F. (President and Mrs.), 1960-1966 (Box 9, Folder 235)
  Optional Feature Health Insurance Plan for the Aged, Social Security (draft not sent), civil defense, land vs. parks and recreational purposes, traffic accident prevention, 52nd Annual National Convention Speech, condolences on death of John Fitzgerald Kennedy's father, international trade policy, problems on narcotics, foreign affairs, Saratoga Performing Arts Center, Mrs. Kenndy unable to attend.
- Kennedy, Robert F. (Mr. & Mrs.), 1966-1969 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  Programs for the mentally retarded, report; "Robert Kennedy Strikes Out - for Power;" NAR's report on Electric Power Commission; invitation to Ethel Kennedy to State dinner honoring astronauts.
- Kheel, Theodore, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 237)
  Port Authority mass transit, New York & New Jersey.
- Kimball, Arthur A., 1959-1969 (Box 10, Folder 238)
  Information about White House procedures, report on three President's Advisory Committee on Government Organization items, farm speech in Minnesota, National Labor Relations Board, racial problems, Nixon Administration.
- King, Jean L. (Mrs.), 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 239)
  Assistant to Director, Institute for Interdisciplinary Studies, Federal system.
- Kintner, Robert E., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 241)
  President, National Broadcasting Company, trip to Latin America.
- Kintner, William, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 242)
  Appeal for Conference on Transatlantic Technological Collaboration, congratulations on being named Ambassador to Thailand.
- Kirk, John P., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 243)
  President, Universal Heritage Investments Corporation, request for information on Jackson Leighter.
- Kirwan, William E., 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 244)
  Superintendent, New York State Police, Students for a Democratic Society vs. Communist Party, students rioting, appeal for promotion of Joe Blair.
- Kissinger, Henry A. - 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 245)
  The Petroleum Allocation Program Report, President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board, U.S.-Japanese relations, meeting in the State Department on Brazil, U.S.-Soviet relations, Special Task force on Debt Service, General Porter comments on military missions in Latin America, bill to create new undersecretary position, Guam Doctrine, Latin American treaty, political exchange program with Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, Nixon's Organization of American States speech, biographical data, George Duckwitz, statement on Czechoslovakia, foreign affairs, personal correspondence.
- Kissinger, Henry A. - 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 246)
  Speech on World Organization, Special Studies, A Commission for America's Future, Task Force on the Conduct of Foreign Relations, John Foster Dulles Oral History Project, Rockefeller Panel Reports, Foreign Policy Research Institute, 1965 Report on Germany, Vietnam policy, Harvard International Seminar, personal correspondence.
- Kissinger, Henry A. - 1959-1963 (Box 10, Folder 247)
  Disarmament, North Atlantic Treaty Organization policies, Civil Defense Action, Godkin Lectures at Harvard, State Department research organization, views on meeting with German Chancellor Konrad Adenauer, advice on speeches on international affairs, American Council on Germany, personal correspondence.
- Knowles, John H. (Dr.), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 248)
  China situation.
- Knox, Seymour H., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 249)
  Albright-Knox Art Gallery opening of Michael Rockefeller's art exhibit, list of organizations receiving grants.
- Kollek, Teddy, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 250)
  Mayor of Jerusalem, Israel, museum being built with funds from Rockefeller Foundation, Arab-Israeli War.
- Kosygin, Aleksei N., 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 251)
  Appeals for visit permissions and visas.
- Krupsak, Mary Anne, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 252)
  Conference on "Women - A Political Force."
- Kuchel, Thomas H. (The Honorable), 1963-1968 (Box 10, Folder 253)
  Nation's water and power potential, support during primary campaign in California, support during scandal, personal correspondence.
- Kunstler, William, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 254)
  Black Panthers' lawyer.
- L General (Box 11, Folder 255)
  Labanowski, Phyllis: 1966, picture of NAR. Laird, Melvin: 1964, Wisconsin Congressman, Republican Convention. Lamont, Austin: 1965, thanks for NAR's contribution. Lancaster, Bruce: 1963, State Department, Officer in Charge, Argentine Affairs, briefing materials. Landauer, James: 1958-1959, congratulations to NAR. Landinez, Giminez: 1966, Venezuelan politician, seeks appointment with NAR. Lane, Myles (Mr. & Mrs.): 1970, NAR thanks. Langley, June Pickens: 1963, request for license plate. Lankler, Alexander: 1965-1967, Organization of American States, appointment with the Mayor of Florence, Italy. Lapham, Robert R.: 1964, Special Agent, U.S. Secret Service, reference check. Larimore, Granville (Dr.): 1967, Deputy Commissioner, New York State Health Department. Larson, Arthur: 1968, writing book, NAR permission to use information in book on Dwight D. Eisenhower. Lavalle, Paul: 1966, Arts & Entertainment Committee. Lavon, P.: 1959, funding for project of Israeli General Federation of Labor. Lawley, James R.: 1967-1969, Regional Coordinator, New York State Republican State Committee, Senator Goodell, transportation bond issue, redistricting. Lawrence, Charles D.: 1967, membership in Knickerbocker Club. Lawrence, David: 1959, editor, "U.S. News & World Report," NAR praise for article. Lea, Charles A.: 1959, Central Intelligence Agency agent in New York State. Leeds, Laurence C.: 1967, Chairman, Patrons Committee, 66th Assembly District Republican Club. Lefferts, Cynthia: 1965-1966, Governor's Awards Program, Council on the Arts. Lefkowitz, Barry: 1968, seeks NAR involvement in high school politics project. Legendre, Michel: 1968-1970, French Ambassador to Pakistan, sends gifts. Leidesdorf, Samuel D.: 1959, NAR United Jewish Appeal contribution. Leisure, George S.: 1962, President, Children's Village, Rockefeller Brothers Fund gift. Leithead, Barry T.: 1960, treasurer, "Dinner with Ike." Leonard, Bill: 1965-1967, Columbia Broadcasting System Director of News, NAR modern art series. Leoni, Raul: 1965, Venzuela. Leopold, Alice: 1966, Republican Party Policy Coordinating Committee.
- L General (Box 11, Folder 256)
  Levine, Alvin (Mrs.): 1967, appeal, declined. Levine, Mickey: 1960, American Veterans Committee. Levy, Herbert: 1966, Invitation to NAR for lunch. Levy, Marilyn: 1970, real estate venture, Jackie Robinson. Lewthwaite, Margaret Edmons (Mrs.): 1964, Paris exhibit. Lindbeck, John D. (Dr.): 1964, East Asian Institute, Columbia University. Lingua, George: 1967, President, National Kidney Foundation, appeal. Link, Eugene P.: 1966, Michael Rockefeller Scholarship. Linkletter, Art: 1969, thanks for gifts. Lippman, Walter: 1968, columnist. Lobl, Dorie: 1972, thanks to NAR. Loeb, John (Mr. & Mrs.): 1960-1966, New York Nixon Campaign, 1960 purchase, New York road problem, personal correspondence. Loeb, Leon: 1965, President, Sound Studios, Inc., sends tape. Logan, Joshua (Mrs.): 1967, invitation to NAR, declined. Logan, Leighton: 1967, Secretary, Board of Directors, Sleepy Hollow Cemetery. Lomas, Malcolm (Mr. & Mrs.): 1967, NAR thanks. Lorber, Herbert J.: 1959, gift to NAR. Lord, Gay Patterson: 1964, thanks for gift. Lord, Oswald B. (Mrs.): 1966, Senator John Sherman Cooper campaign appeal. Loring, Herbert R. (Dr.): 1962, Missouri School of Religion, sent essay. Losee, Tom: 1960, NAR TV program ratings. Louria, Donald B. (Dr.): 1967, Vietnam War. Love, John: 1967, Governor of Colorado, Rupblican Governors' Conference. Lowery, Robert B.: 1959, NAR thanks. Lowry, James I. (Rev.): 1967, Minister, First Presbyterian Church, Henderson, Kentucky. Lubin, Isador (Dr.): 1959, visited Monte Sacro, sends photos. Luce, Henry R. & Clare Booth: 1959-1966, congratulations, sends books, personal correspondence. Luckman, Charles: 1967, seeks appointment with NAR, declined. Lumbard, Eliot H.: 1967, Counsel to Government Federal Bureau of Investigation activities. Lumet, Sidney (Mrs.): 1972, appeal, Dance Theater of Harlem. Lyden, G. Collins: 1964-1967, Campaign Director, Albany County Republican Campaign Committee. Lynd, Dorothy: 1963, thanks.
- L General (Box 11, Folder 0256A)
- Larrabee, Eric, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 257)
  Budget, New York State Council on the Arts.
- Lasker, Bernard J., 1965-1973 (Box 11, Folder 258)
  Contribution to Lindsay Finance Committee, Port Authority.
- Lavine, Abe, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 259)
  Civil Service, Medicaid.
- Lefkowitz, Louis J. (The Honorable), 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 260)
  Salaries, personal correspondence.
- Lehman, Maxwell (Professor), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 261)
  New York City Revision Commission.
- Levine, Louis L. (The Honorable), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 262)
  Industrial Commissioner, New York State Department of Labor, United States investigation.
- Levitt, Arthur, 1961-1973 (Box 11, Folder 263)
  New York State Comptroller, state budget & finances.
- Levy, Gustave, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 264)
  Metropolitan Transit Authority financing, Museum of Modern Art, Port Authority, personal.
- Lewis, Hobart, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 265)
  Editor-in-Chief, "Readers Digest," 50th Anniversary.
- Liebowitz, Samuel (Judge), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 266)
  McGovern comments.
- Lindsay, John V., 1964-1971 (Box 11, Folder 267)
  United States Congressman, New York City Mayor, NAR 1964 Campaign, New York City land use, drug program, education, revenue sharing, city-state relations.
- Linowitz, Sol M., 1968-1973 (Box 11, Folder 268)
  Organization of American States, Urban Development Corporation, Watergate.
- Little, Margaret (Mrs.), 1967-1971 (Box 11, Folder 269)
  Secretary to (U.S. Department of ) Housing and Urban Development Secretary Romney.
- Littlefield, Jacqueline (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 270)
  International art auction.
- Lockwood, John, 1955-1969 (Box 11, Folder 271)
  NAR loan, Republican & legislative politics.
- Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1959-1964 (Box 11, Folder 272)
  United States Ambassador to the United Nations, 1960 Vice Presidential candidate, Ambassador to South Vietnam, Director, Atlantic Institute, Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, economy, 1960 election, South Vietnam.
- Loeb, John L. (Jr.), 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 273)
  Seeks post in NAR administration.
- Logan, Arthur C. (Dr.) (Box 11, Folder 274)
  New York City Government, patronship of art exhibit.
- Logue, Edward J., 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 275)
  President, Urban Development Corporation, acceptance of post, Westchester, New York City welfare housing, federal housing moratorium, New York State financial problems, personnel.
- Lomenzo, John P., 1963-1974 (Box 12, Folder 276)
  New York State Secretary of State, politics, dismissal of Mario Biaggi, criminal investigation of Lomenzo.
- Lounsbury, John H., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 277)
  United States Department of Agriculture re: NAR property.
- Lubell, Samuel, 1964-1972 (Box 12, Folder 278)
  NAR presidential campaign; 1968, 1970 senatorial & gubernatorial elections, public opinion pollster.
- M General (Box 12, Folder 279)
  MacArthur, Helen Hayes: 1967, congratulations to NAR. MacCrate, Robert: 1959-1962, staff, Long Island Rail Road strike, NAR veto, health insurance & housing, racing. MacDonald, Alletta (Mrs.): 1959, traffic ticket. MacIntyre, Malcolm Ames (Mrs.): 1968, contribution to Tie Line, international exchange group. Macrae, Elliot B.: 1965, NAR thanks. Macy, John W. Jr.: 1968, Chairman, Civil Service Commission, offers candidate for position. Maffry, August: 1963, policy question. Magsaysay, Jesus: 1962, NAR thanks. Mahaney, Francis X.: 1968, Manager, Special Projects, "The Washington Post," New York State advertisement for Nixon inauguration. Majekodummi, M. A. (Dr.): 1970, Nigerian official. Majewski, Lawrence J.: 1970, NAR contribution to New York University. Makary: 1973, Bishop of Uman. Makla, Robert M.: 1969, NAR & Rockefeller family contribution to New York City. Malone, John: 1967, Public Relations, New York State Teachers Association, NAR speech notes, newsletter. Malott, Deane W.: 1961, President, Cornell University, NAR art donation. Malpass, John R.: 1960-1961, son's West Point application. Manchester, William: 1967, NAR thanks for book. Manley, A. Bruce: 1968, Commissioner, Department of Taxation and Finance, congratulations, Thruway job. Marano, Luigi: 1969, Family Court Judge, promotion. March, Frank: 1966, Publisher & Editor, "Bronx-Westchester Life." Marchi, John: 1964, State Senator, Staten Island Little League. Marcuccilli, Orazio (Mr. & Mrs.): 1963, appeal. Marcus, Stanley: 1968, Nieman-Marcus Department Store. Mariani, Louis: 1967, wishes for health. Markel, Lester: 1960, public opinion project. Marshall, John Lee: 1960, son of NAR aide. Marshall, Thurgood: 1967, U. S. Supreme Court Justice, trip to Caneel Bay. Marsters, Alton K.: 1962, Vice President, Bausch & Lomb, Inc., thanks for gift. Martin, Dave: 1962, Nebraska Congressman. Martin, E.B. (Mrs.): 1965, her son's trip to New Guinea. Marx, David: 1966-1968, sends Christmas toys. Mason, Anna G.: 1960, thanks for gifts. Massolo, Arthur: 1967-1968, staff, history of 1966 campaign. Mathews, J. H. (Mr. & Mrs.): 1967, Manager, JY Ranch, Wyoming. NAR thanks for trip. Matisse, Pierre: 1966, personal correspondence. Matson: 1966, New York City Fire Department Battalion Chief, false alarm at 812 Fifth Avenue. Matter, Mercedes (Mrs.): 1966, original Whitney Museum. Matteson, Robert: 1964, appointment with NAR re: disarmament. Mattioli, Raffaele (Dr.): 1966, banker, NAR thanks for wine. Mauze, James F.: 1968, Missouri politics. May, Stacy: 1959-1964, staff, trade with Communist nations, New York State Tax Study, coherent U. S. economic policy, economic research. Mazzilli, Paschoal Ranieri: 1964, President of Brazil.
- M General (Box 12, Folder 280)
  McAlpin, David H.: 1968-1969, Caneel Bay Plantation. McAuliffe, David H.: 1960, Office of Vice President for Personnel and Public Relations, American Cyanamid Company. McCabe, Charles B.: 1960, Publisher, "New York Mirror," contribution. McCabe, Tom: no date, Eisenhower Exchange Fellowship Dinner. McCall, Robert B.: 1966, Assistant to the Governor of Idaho, sends NAR, Jr. clipping. McCallum, David: 1967, Metro-Goldwyn Mayer, Inc. visit to studio. McCann, Gerard B.: 1967, Deputy Assistant to the Director, U. S. Secret Service, personal correspondence. McCardle, Marcia: 1963, thank you for gift. McCarthy, Frank: 1960, financial needs of the George C. Marshall Research Center. McCarthy, Ursula (Mrs.): 1968, appeal. McClintock, Robert: 1972, United States Ambassador to Venezuela. McClory, Robert: 1959, Representative, State of Illinois, personal correspondence. McCloy, John J.: 1961-1967, Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. McCone, John A.: 1962-1963, Director, Central Intelligence Agency, security problems. McCoy, Georgia: 1959, (U.S. Department of) Health, Education, and Welfare, appointment with NAR. McCracken, Robert J.: 1971, donation to Riverside Church. McDermott, Gene (Mr. & Mrs.): no date, wish to see paintings at NAR's apartment. McDonnell, Vincent D.: 1966, Chairman, New York State Board of Mediation, NAR's handling of strike. McInnes, M. G.: 1966, visit to ranch in Venezuela. McGinnis, Paul D.: 1959-1966, Commissioner, New York State Department of Correction. McGoohan, Patrick: 1967, Metro-Goldwyn Mayer, Inc., visit to studios. McGrath, Christopher C.: 1966, Bronx County Republican Dinner. McGregor, Constance: 1968, congratulations on running again for governor. McKeldin, Theodore R.: 1966-1967, Mayor of Baltimore, Maryland. McKeon, Richard P. (Dr.): 1959, note on serious accident. McKinney, Laurence: 1962, thank you. McKinnon, Genevieve L.: 1966, dedication to work. McLane, Charles: 1968, thank you. McLaughlin, J. Frank (Mrs.): 1962, thank you for sympathy note. McMahan, Linda: 1968, film, "Portrait of a Governor." McMorran, J. Burch: 1959-1969, Commissioner, New York State Department of Transportation. McNutt, Albert H.: 1963-1968, Uruguay, personal correspondence. Meade, Robert C.: 1969, Supervisor, town of North Hempstead, transportation problems on Long Island. Meads, Donald: 1967, President, International Basic Economy Corporation Packing Co, Inc. Mellon, G. A.: 1960, thank you. Menk, Anthony: 1965, thank you. Merrow, Chester E.: 1959, U. S. House of Representatives, thank you. Meskill, Thomas J.: 1972, Governor of Connecticut, Goodspeed Opera. Metcalf, George R.: 1966, reference to a study on ghettos. Meyer, Kirt: 1959, congratulations.
- M General (Box 12, Folder 281)
  Miles, Arnold: 1964, wedding invitation, declined. Miller, Herbert J.: 1973, Member of Assembly, requests interview. Miller, J. Irwin: 1969, Republican Governors' Conference in Lexington, Kentucky, offers hospitality. Miller, L.S.: 1967, reference for press secretary. Miller, Peter P. (Mrs.): 1958, Women's Republican Club. Miller, Robert H.: 1963, Chairman, Chautauqua County Republican Committee, appointments. Milliken, Minot K.: 1963, sends autographed photo. Milone, Joseph J.: 1966, dinner, Village of Mamaroneck, New York. Minges, James S.: 1966: seeking information on Frank A. Waugh and his contribution to Landscape Architecture and Planning. Minster of Agriculture, Brazil: 1964, American International Association. Minshall, William E.: 1969, United States Representative, sends news clipping of Mr. & Mrs. NAR. Mintener, Susan: 1963, wedding, thanks for gift. Minton, Lee W.: 1965-1967, seeks repeal of Section 14b of Taft-Hartley Act. Mocsanyi, Paul: 1967, permission to use NAR lecture "Collectors and Collecting." Moerdler, Charles G.: 1965, New York Young Republicans Club. Moley, Raymond: 1966, Contributing Editor, "Newsweek," supports candidacy. Monahan, Robert S.: 1959, New Hampshire support. Montano, Marianne: 1967, Braun & Co., photos, thanks. Montilla, Ricardo (Dr.): 1967, NAR's acknowlegement of gift. Moore, Charles F. (Jr.): 1964-1966, Brookside Congregational Church, Manchester, New Hampshire, copy of sermon delivered by Dr. T Merton Rymph, personal correspondence. Moore, Frank C.: 1960-1970, President, Government Affairs Foundation, Inc., recommendation on salary of Dr. Hamilton, State University of New York, contribution to organization, personal correspondence. Moore, George S.: 1959, Executive Vice President, The First National City Bank of New York, proposed legislation to permit foreign banks to have branches in New York. Moore, Jonathan: 1967, Institute of Politics, Harvard University, taking job with George Romney. Morgan, A. K.: 1962, Chief Engineer & General Manager, Palisades Interstate Park Commission.
- M General (Box 13, Folder 282)